But... Adagaki Aki didn't remember it.
So then...
Why do you call me Pig's Foot?
Of course, I don't have any proof.
The Cruel Princess could just be playing dumb.
But I want to hear it
from you personally, Master.
No.
Right. I mean, all this time...
We were in this together.
You're such an idiot, Pig's Foot.
I'd never do that.
O-Of course not.
I'm lying.
Huh?
#4 "I'm Not Going to Fall in Love with You, Pig's Foot"
Aki-chan, where should we go?
Is there anywhere you want to go?
You can't expect me to decide so suddenly.
O-Of course. Just take
your time and think about it.
Let you spend time with Aki-sama alone?!
Yes. I have something very
important to tell her.
You'd better not be trying to do
something sleazy to Aki-sama!
Of course not.
I mean, I just said I'd wait until
she sorted out her feelings.
Then why did you say out of the blue
that you wanted to be alone with her?
Aki-sama clearly seems depressed.
Are you sure you're not using this
as an excuse to get closer to her?
It's the opposite!
It's because Aki-chan's in that state that
I'm going to try to separate her
from Makabe Masamune for good.
B-But how?
I know! We have that picture of
Koiwai Yoshino and Makabe Masamune.
Let's start spreading rumors of things
that may or may not have
happened and ruin his image!
I considered that, too,
but that's the last resort.
Why, though?!
Even if she found out about
Makabe and Koiwai Yoshino,
Aki-chan's relationship with Koiwai Yoshino
wouldn't be the worst it can be.
But if we try to make it worse,
Aki-chan's the one who'll be hurt.
True. If Aki-sama and Koiwai Yoshino's
relationship were to completely fall apart,
it'd prove difficult to get Aki-sama
back on her feet, even for us.
Though I hate to admit that...
Aki-chan isn't the one we're
supposed to be attacking.
Makabe is.
Not to mention, even if we deliberately
try to separate Makabe from Aki-chan,
our hard work will be wasted
if Koiwai Yoshino gets in the way.
That's why our first priority is to make sure
Koiwai Yoshino doesn't get in the way.
And then, we'll get Aki-chan to
stop hanging out with Makabe.
I'll be the one to make sure that happens.
But knowing Koiwai Yoshino,
she'll catch on if we take too long.
I need you three to act first and make
sure she doesn't get near Aki-chan.
All right.
I do feel bad for Aki-sama,
but this is for her own good.
Let's do this!
Just you wait, Koiwai Yoshino!
Yup, yup.
Let's think up a sabotage plan.
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Still, there's no guarantee with this plan.
We have to go to a place where we know for sure
that neither Koiwai Yoshino
nor Makabe will show up.
Aki-chan, would you like to go there?
Huh?
Sure.
Well, no time like the present!
Wait a sec.
Aki-sama
I'm going to head to the Ferris wheel
N-No way...
But why?!
The reason's simple.
Because... It's because I...
hated you so much, I could die.
You've got chickenpox.
It's highly contagious, so make sure
you stay away from Aki-sama.
You can't leave this room.
How long?
Until you're completely better.
Make sure you tell Aki-sama
to stay out of this room, too.
Understood.
It's fine if I can't see Aki-sama...
I'm free.
Back then, I was at constantly at the mercy
of Aki-sama's endless bad moods.
Mom, I can't go outside today, either?
I don't have a fever anymore.
Not yet.
How many more days?
We'll just have to wait and see.
It's so quiet.
I don't even have anything to add to my diary.
Kids' Study Notebook
Picture Diary
Kids' Study Guide
Weather: Sunny
Handkerchief
Aki-sama made fun of the
handkerchief Mom made for me.
She said it looked poor
and that made it weird.
Weather: Sunny
Fireworks
Aki-sama suddenly said she
wanted to try an experiment
with skyrocket fireworks to see
if she could send someone
to the moon with them.
I was scared.
Fireworks are scary...
I've only written stuff about Aki-sama, anyway.
I ended up crying because Aki-sama
cut the hair off my favorite doll.
But my mom told me to just deal with it.
Aki-sama might be bored, too,
because she has no one to make her plaything.
Is she mad? Is she sulking?
Maybe she's even crying.
No, no, no!
Aki-sama's someone I have to take care of.
Even if I'm not around...
Come on! Try harder, Masamune!
Aki-sama?
If you stop, Sean will catch up to you!
I can't do this anymore!
Then give up and get along with him.
A boy I don't know...
I guess she can find a plaything to
order around whenever she wants.
But he's doomed.
He's just going to get yelled
at and bullied by Aki-sama.
Poor thing.
Yay!
Looks like we caught you, Masamune!
Yeah, I guess you did.
I think I was in shock.
I thought I was the only one
who could keep up with Aki-sama.
And yet... he seemed so much happier than me.
I could tell...
that he...
really liked Aki-sama.
Did she get Yoshino's
chickenpox after this long?
Well, she has been playing
outside quite often lately.
Maybe she caught some unknown bug.
Yoshino, keep an eye on Aki-sama.
Are you okay, Aki-sama?
Is this your fault, Yoshino?
I don't know.
This is awful. I hate being in this room.
Too many of Mom and Dad's things are in here.
You can't even take care of your own daughter?!
I can say the same exact thing about you!
Sir, Madam, Aki-sama is trying to rest...
You're the one who was by her side!
Would you shut up already?!
They said "divorce" means that my mom
and dad won't be married anymore.
Mom's going to leave me...
She says she can't help it
because of a trial or something...
Is Aki-sama... crying?
But I'm not alone anymore.
Because I have Masamune.
I'll be okay.
Hey, Aki-sama...
What about me?
I'd worked so hard...
I'd done everything she told me
to do ever since I was born.
Because... that's what I was told to do.
And yet...
Aki-chan!
That voice...
Aki-chan! Aki-chan!
Aki-chan!
This loser's trying to get that
boss girl to save him again?
Talk about pathetic!
Aki-chan...
Aki-chan!
Aki-chan! Aki-chan!
After that, you stopped coming around,
and it was a huge weight off my shoulders.
He's white as a sheet. I guess I can't blame him.
Everything he thought he knew is
being destroyed down to its core.
But it wasn't good for Aki-sama.
She fell apart.
She cried every day and ended up hating boys.
I regretted my actions
for the first time in my life.
I realized that I did something
I never should have done.
I looked for that boy for a really long time,
but I could never find him.
When I thought there was nothing
I could do to make up for it...
Wait, where?
Hey, look! He's apparently a transfer student!
Go talk to him!
Makabe Masamune-kun is so cool!
Masamune...
There you were.
I knew right away that it was you, Pig's Foot.
You recognized me right away?
Even though Adagaki Aki couldn't?
Aki-sama's a bit dense.
Please forgive her for that.
That's just how powerful
your old image is in her mind.
And...
I ended up helping you out
because you remembered Aki-sama.
I figured it could be the way
to make it up to Aki-sama.
Hey, wait a minute!
How is that making it up to her?
I'm trying to get revenge here!
I was going to make her fall for
me just so I could dump her!
Even you said...
If you dump her, and that makes
her a little more modest,
it greatly benefits me,
as well as Aki-sama.
I'm sorry.
I didn't actually want you to dump her.
Because...
you can't hate Aki-sama when you've seen her
for who she truly is, right?
I...
Right now, Aki-sama is...
on a date with Kanetsugu.
She still thinks he's Pig's Foot.
I can't make any moves
because my parents and some other
people are keeping their eye on me.
So, Pig's Foot...
I need you to save Aki-sama.
Damn it!
Yes, go, Pig's Foot...
To Aki-sama.
I'm an idiot.
Master is also an idiot!
Everyone is a big, huge idiot!
Okay, we got this far.
Now, how do I take the first step?
What's wrong?
Huh? Er, I was just thinking how I finally
got to be alone with you, Aki-chan.
Right...
Ugh, what is Yoshino doing?
Sorry, Aki-chan.
But I need to get guaranteed additional
funds from your family, no matter what.
But considering I was already getting funding,
I knew it would've proved
difficult if I asked for more.
That's why I need you to
personally ask your family.
That would mean
you'd have to accept the Adagaki and Gasou
families being connected by marriage.
But I'm very aware...
that the shadow of a certain man
continues to live in your heart.
And I need to make that shadow
disappear here and now,
in order to protect my own happiness.
Makabe?!
You three...
Wh-What the heck is he doing here?!
I-I have no idea!
But we have to stop him, too!
But what if Koiwai Yoshino gets
to Aki-sama in the meantime?
Perfect timing!
Do you know where
Kanetsugu and Adagaki Aki are?
Like we'd ever tell you, you cheater!
Cheater?
We are aware that you have been having
secret rendezvous with Koiwai Yoshino.
So what exactly are you planning
to tell Aki-sama right now?
See? You're speechless!
Now stay away from Aki-sama!
Shut up!
Wh-What did you just say?!
I have no intention of clearing up
these little misunderstandings.
If you're going to call me trash,
that's fine, because it's true.
But...
Who's going to save Adagaki Aki
from Gasou Kanetsugu's lies?
Gasou Kanetsugu's...
...lies?
If you really care about Aki-sama, answer me.
Where are those two right now?
So what exactly are you planning
to tell Aki-sama right now?
What am I planning to tell Adagaki Aki?
This is good, too.
Fresh Ice Cream
Want to take a little break?
Really? Let me try some.
I want to go on the roller coaster.
Let's go!
I wonder if I'm tall enough.
You dropped it?
Oh, jeez...
Here.
Thanks, Onii-chan.
Don't drop it again, okay?
'Kay.
Here you go, Aki-chan.
Thanks.
You finally smiled.
Did I seem that unfriendly?
No, I wouldn't say so.
But you've been trying to
act tough for a while.
If this is helping you relax, I'm glad.
You're really good at calming people
down, or making them a bit kinder.
Really? Maybe it's because
I have a little sister.
Your little sister's still in the hospital, right?
Yes.
Is there anything I can do to help?
I'd feel bad for asking. I'm already
causing you enough trouble...
And I wouldn't be able to return the favor.
That's not true, Kane—
Masamune. You came back to me.
Of course I'd help you!
So, really... Ask me for anything.
Um, Aki-chan...
Actually—
Makabe?!
Quit using my damn name!
Please... reach Aki-sama in time.
Please let these feelings
that started with hatred
be something I can let go of here and now.
Wait, Makabe! What are you doing?!
Then there's you!
Even if this is all just a
giant misunderstanding,
I can't let your current ugly
personality off the hook!
Ug—
So really...
If you're gonna go out with someone like him...
Go out with the real...
Go out with me instead!